One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Wealth, fame, power...
Zenginlik, şöhret, güç...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates, obtained everything the world has to offer.
Dünyanın sunabileceği her şeyi elde eden adam, Korsanlar Kralı, Gold Roger.
What he said in his final moments drove countless souls to the seas.
Son sözleri dünyanın her yerinden maceracıları denize çekti.
You want my treasure?
Hazinem mi?
Go ahead.
İstiyorsanız, alabilirsiniz.
Find it!
Arayıp bulun!
Everything is right where I left it!
Bu dünyanın sunabileceği her şeyi orada bıraktım!
People set their sights on the Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams.
Artık herkes, hayallerinin peşinde Grand Line’a yelken açıyor!
The world has truly entered the Great Pirate Era!
Dünya, Büyük Korsan Çağı'na girdi!
Come aboard and bring along all your hopes and dreams
Atlayın gemiye, getirin umut ve hayallerinizi
I know together we'll find everything we're looking for Sagashi mono wo sagashi ni yuku no sa
Birlikte bulacağız aradığımız her şeyi
One Piece! ONE PIECE
One Piece!
Compasses? Not for me. Left them all behind Rashinban nante juutai no moto
Pusulayı geride bırak, sadece yavaşlatır bizi
I'm headed out to sea, with my heart serving as guide Netsu ni ukasare kaji wo toru no sa
Kalbini dinle, yelken aç, dümeni sen tut.
Following the ancient map to the spot marked "X" reveals Hokori kabutteta takara no chizu mo
Haritanın sonunda beliren o efsanevi yer,
Yeah, it's only legendary till someone proves it's real Tashikameta no nara densetsu janai!
gerçekliği kanıtlanınca efsane olmaktan çıkar!
When the world's got you down,
Tüm zorluklara rağmen, acılara,
lean on your crew, they'll turn it around
hüzünlere ve yürekteki yaralara inat
Their biorhythm will carry you through BIORHYTHM nokkatte
Bil ki, hep yanında olacağım
We're gonna make the most of it Omoi sugoseba ii!
Senin de yapacağını bildiğim gibi!
Come aboard and bring along all your hopes and dreams Arittake no yume wo kaki atsume
Atlayın gemiye, getirin umut ve hayallerinizi
I know together we'll find everything we're looking for Sagashi mono wo sagashi ni yuku no sa
Birlikte bulacağız aradığımız her şeyi
Got some change to my name, POCKET no COIN
Eğer arkadaşım olmak istersen,
and maybe you wanna be my friend? Soreto YOU WANNA BE MY FRIEND?
her zaman yer var senin için
We are, we are on the cruise! WE ARE, WE ARE ON THE CRUISE!
Biz, hepimiz dalgaların üstündeyiz!
WE ARE!
HEPİMİZ!
For Whom the Bell Tolls
Çanlar Kimin İçin Çalacak?
H-He just...
O-O çocuk...
He broke Captain Kuro's cat claw!
Kaptan Kuro'nun kedi pençesini kırdı!
Only five of these weird sword things left!
Şu tuhaf kılıçlarından sadece beş tane kaldı.
It's okay! He has plenty of fight left in him!
Sorun yok! Hâlâ dövüşebilir!
Yeah! He's still got the other claw!
Evet! Diğer pençesi hâlâ duruyor!
Scratch him up and kill him, Captain Kuro!
O herifi doğra, Kaptan Kuro!
Whoa, you can't call him that anymore!
Hey! O isim yasaklı!
Oh yeah... I think his name in the village was Klaha... something...
Buralarda Klaha bilmem ne diye bilindiğinden eminim...
Mr. Klah, then!
Kla-san, diyelim!
– Mr. Klah! Get 'im!
– Kla-san! Hakla onu!
Would you all just...
Lanet çenenizi...
shut the hell up?!
kapatın lan!
Come on out, you twerps!
Çıkın ortaya, sizi bücürler!
I know you're hiding in there!
Orada saklandığınızı biliyorum!
Give it up already!
Pes edin artık!
Come over here!
Bu tarafa!
We'll take you straight to her!
Seni doğruca Kaya-san'a götüreceğiz!
You really think I'm that gullible? As if I'd trust anything you brats say!
Cidden o kadar enayi miyim? Sanki siz veletlerin dediğine inanırım da!
Huh?!
Ha?!
We got him!
Yakaladık!
Now!
Şimdi!
Take this!
Al bakalım!
Pepper Attack!
Toz Biber Saldırısı!
– Push!
– İtin!
Owww!
Ahhh!
Ow! Ow!
Ah! Ah!
– It's over, hypnotist!
– İşin bitti, hipnozcu!
Don't get cocky.
Ukalalık etmeyin.
Darn it! We failed...!
Kahretsin! Başaramadık...!
You've made a mockery of me.
Beni ciddiye almadınız.
But I am still a pirate...
Sonuçta ben bir korsanım.
– Onion!
– Tamanegi!
You wannabe pirate brats poked your noses in a bit too deep...
Korsan taklidi yapan bebeler, yanlış kişilere bulaştınız...
Where are you hiding, Miss?!
Nerede saklanıyorsun, hanımefendi?
I'll start by executing these three.
Önce bu üçünü öldüreceğim.
You can reflect on your poor choice to meddle with real pirates...
Gerçek korsanlara bulaşmanın bedelini...
on your way to the afterlife.
öbür dünyaya giderken anlayacaksınız.
There you are.
İşte oradasın.
No!
Yapmayın!
Run, Miss Kaya!
Kaçın, Kaya-san!
Hey!
Hey!
Yeah! That's them!
Evet! Onların sesi!
It's the other way?!
O taraftan mı?!
I'll eliminate each and every one of you later...
Hepinizi daha sonra yok edeceğim.
That includes Jango!
Tabii Jango'yu da!
Wh-Why us?!
N-Niye ki?!
Please stop joking around, Captain Kuro!
Lütfen şaka yapmayı bırakın, Kaptan Kuro!
It's still not too late for us to attack the village, right?!
Köye saldırmak için hâlâ geç kalmadık, değil mi?!
And if Captain Jango gets her to write her will, your plan will succeed!
Kaptan Jango da istediğiniz vasiyeti yazdırırsa, planınız başarılı olacak!
Do not concern yourselves with the details of my plan...
Artık plan için endişelenmenize gerek yok.
All I need from you are corpses on which to pin the blame.
Cesetleriniz burada olduğu sürece, masumiyetimi kanıtlayabilirim.
I never intended to let any of you leave this village alive.
Zaten başından beri bu köyden ayrılmanızı planlamamıştım.
I can't let anyone who knows my true identity live.
Gerçek kimliğimi bilen kimsenin yaşamasına izin veremem.
No way...
Olamaz!
Then you planned to kill us from the very start?!
Yani çoktan hepimizi öldürmeyi planladınız mı?
That's right...
Aynen öyle...
For three long years now, back when I was still going by Captain Kuro...
Bunu üç yıl önce, hâlâ Kaptan Kuro’yken planlamıştım.
it was all...
Hepsi...
it was all part of my plan!
Hepsi planımın bir parçası!
Man, you guys are dumb.
Hepiniz aptalsınız.
Your pirate crew is so lame!
Korsan tayfanız o kadar vasat ki!
"Lame"?
"Vasat" mı?
In the end, a pirate crew is nothing but a pack of stray dogs!
Korsan tayfaları, medeni toplumlar için uygun olmayan bir köpek sürüsüdür.
What could they possibly accomplish without a plan?!
Çobansız bir sürü ne yapabilir ki?!
Every last one should just shut up and follow my orders!
Herkes çenesini kapatıp emirlerime uymalı!
Crew members are a captain's loyal pawns!
Tayfa üyeleri, bir kaptanın sadık piyonlarıdır!
I'm the one who decides whether to kill them or spare them.
Yaşamaları veya ölmeleri bana kalmış!
No matter how great the obstacle, they simply need to stand up to it...
Karşılarına ne engel çıkarsa çıksın, dimdik durup...
and die according to my plans.
planıma uygun şekilde gebermeleri gerek.
This is what it means to be a pirate!
Korsan olmak budur!
Don't patronize me, you little vagrant!
Bana vaaz vermeye kalkma, seni başıboş köpek!
Even if a captain like you...
Senin gibi bir kaptanın...
had hundreds or thousands of men following him...
yüzlerce hatta binlerce adamı olsa bile...
you'd never be better than Usopp!
Usopp kadar taşaklı olamazsın!
What?!
Ne dedin?!
You're saying I'm inferior to a kid pretending to be a pirate captain?
O kaptan bozması benden daha taşaklı mı?
That's right!
Kesinlikle!
How droll!
Ne kadar komiksin!
Don't get cocky just because you snapped one of my claws!
Pençelerimden birini kırdın diye kendini bir şey sanma!
How exactly is he better than me?!
Nasıl daha taşaklıymış?!
Let's hear it!
Söylesene!
Character.
Karakteriyle.
What?!
Ne?!
You have no idea what it means to be a pirate!
Gerçek bir korsan olmanın manasını bilmiyorsun!
H-He...
O-O...
He kept up with the Pussyfoot Maneuver!
"Kedi Yürüyüşü"nün hızına yetişebiliyor!
How insulting...
Bu ne cüret...
If you're curious about real pirates, then allow me to demonstrate...
Gerçek korsanlardan konuşmak istiyorsan, sana onların dehşetini...
true terror.
göstereyim!
The terror of a pirate who has faced death countless times!
Ölümle sayısız kez karşılaşmış bir korsanın dehşetine şahit olacaksın!
Hey! That stance! Is he...?!
Hey! O duruş! Yoksa...?!
That's the move he's gonna use?!
Onu mu kullanacak?!
But he's only fighting one guy!
Ama sadece biriyle dövüşüyor!
But that's definitely it!
Kesinlikle yapacak!
He's planning to use Whole Nine Yarns!
"Ölüm Kapanı"nı kullanacak!
Aren't we in danger here?!
Burada tehlikede değil miyiz?!
He'll get us, too!
Bizi de haklayacak!
He already plans to kill us!
Zaten bizi öldüreceğini planlamış!
He even said so earlier!
Önceden söyledi!
Please stop, Captain Kuro!
Lütfen durun, Kaptan Kuro!
Anything but that!
Bu şekilde olmasın!
We'll do anything you want!
Ne isterseniz yaparız!
Please, Captain Kuro!
Yalvarıyoruz, Kaptan Kuro!
What's the big deal?
Ne olabilir ki?
He's just swaying back and forth...
Sadece sağa sola sallanıyor...
– Please stop, Captain Kuro!
– Lütfen durun, Kaptan Kuro!
Whole Nine Yarns!
Ölüm Kapanı!
What a pitiful haul...
Bu nasıl ganimet...
I thought they'd have a little more treasure than that...
Bundan daha fazla hazineleri olacağını düşünmüştüm.
Let's see, is the fight over yet?
Bakalım, dövüş bitti mi?
What?
Ne?
Nobody's moving...
Kimse kıpırdamıyor.
Is it over?
Yoksa bitti mi?
There it is!
Orada!
Wh-Why's he over there?!
N-Nasıl orada olabilir?!
Not again!
Yine!
Now it's the wall!
Şimdi de kaya!
Please stop, Captain Kuro!
Lütfen kesin şunu, Kaptan Kuro!
It's no use! His Pussyfoot Maneuver attacks are out of control!
Faydasız! "Kedi Yürüyüşü" saldırıları kontrolden çıktı!
He's moving so fast he doesn't even know what he's slashing!
O kadar hızlı hareket ediyor ki neyi kestiğinden bihaber!
He's already cut down so many of our cr–
Şimdiden birçok adamını biçt–
Hey!
Hey!
Wh-What's happening?!
N-Neler oluyor?!
They're getting all sliced up out of nowhere!
Aniden doğranmaya başladılar!
Show yourself...
Göster kendini...
butler...
uşak...
Don't you care about your crew at all?!
Tayfanı hiç mi umursamıyorsun?!
Luffy...
Luffy...
Found you!
Buldum seni!
Sly bastard!
Sinsi piç!
You should've let me cut you down like a good little boy!
İyi bir çocuk gibi uslu uslu durmalıydın!
Look!
Bak!
My poor men are suffering dearly, and it's all thanks to you!
Senin yüzünden, sevgili adamlarım yarı ölü hâlde.
It would've been kinder if you'd just let my attack kill them!
Onları öldürmeme izin verseydin, daha insancıl olurdu!
Now what?
Şimdi ne var?
You look like you have something to say...
Bir şey mi söyleyeceksin?
Yeah...
Evet...
No matter what...
Asla senin gibi...
I will never be like you.
bir adam olmayacağım.
Never will...?
Olmayacağından değil.
More like never can. Not someone like you, anyway.
Zaten olamazsın. Bu yetenekle olmaz.
Though it doesn't matter...
Ne fark eder ki,
since you're going to die here anyway.
nasılsa burada öleceksin.
Please stop this!
Lütfen kesin şunu!
Leave them alone!
Onları rahat bırak!
I'll write the will!
Vasiyeti yazacağım.
N-No!
H-Hayır!
They'll kill you if you write it, Miss Kaya!
Yazdığınız zaman, sizi öldürecek!
You've got the wrong idea. There are no negotiations to be had here.
Aptal. Benimle müzakere yapma.
Captain Kuro told me to get rid of everyone.
Kaptan Kuro hepinizi öldürmemi istedi.
You can't be serious!
Olamaz!
Do as I say, or I'll take my own life!
Dediğimi yap, yoksa canıma kıyarım!
That means no will!
Vasiyet de olmaz!
Wh-Wh-Whoa! Just hold on!
H-Hayır, hayır! D-Dur... dur!
Don't be hasty!
Aceleci davranma!
I absolutely must get you to write that will!
O vasiyeti kesinlikle yazmalısın!
M-Miss Kaya!
K-Kaya-san!
Fine! The twerps can go!
İyi be! Veletler gidebilir!
Though they're really in no condition to run...
Gerçi kaçacak durumda değiller...
Sign it, too!
Hemen imzala!
I know...
Peki...
"I leave my entire estate to my butler, Klahadore..."
"Tüm servetimi uşağım Klahadore'a bırakıyorum."
Excellent!
Mükemmel!
This is your will, all right!
Görev tamamlandı!
And I didn't even have to hypnotize you!
Seni hipnotize etmeme bile gerek kalmadı!
You promise not to kill them, right?
Onları öldürmeyeceğine söz verdin, tamam mı?
Don't worry.
Endişelenme.
I might not look like it, but I'm a man of my word.
Öyle görünmeyebilirim ama sözümün eriyimdir.
– Miss Kaya!
– Kaya-san!
There they are!
İşte oradalar!
There they are! There they are! Stop!
Oradalar! Oradalar! Dur!
Owww! Ow, ow, ow!
Ahhh! Ah, ah, ah!
That's where I got cut, you know!
Yarama vuruyorsun!
Over there!
Orada!
Alright, I'll be back!
Tamam, sıra bende!
Hey!
Hey!
That's far enough, hypno-freak!
Buraya kadar, seni hipnozcu ucube!
He came after me?!
Peşimden mi gelmiş?!
Guess I'd better finish this quickly!
Bunu hemen bitirsem iyi olacak!
Everything before now was just an appetizer.
Seninle yeterince oynadım.
You get the three-course treatment.
Özel ilgi vakti.
I will baste you in terror and serve you meticulously on a platter!
Seni dehşetle marine edip, özenle servis edeceğim!
Whole Nine Yarns!
Ölüm Kapanı!
Just try that foot technique now!
Şimdi kaçta görelim!
Curses! Get off of me!
Kahretsin! Çekil üstümden!
Now your three-year plan is a complete failure!
Şimdi üç yıllık planın tam bir fiyasko oldu!
What?!
Ne?!
He caught Captain Kuro!
Kaptan Kuro'yu yakaladı!
Hey, if he wins, that means we won't get killed, right?!
Kazanırsa belki de öldürülmeyiz, değil mi?!
Now you die!
Ölme vakti!
Oh, no, you don't!
İzin vermeyeceğiz!
You damn kids!
Lanet olası bücürler!
You're just one step too late, bellyband!
Geç kaldın, kuşaklı adam!
You sure about that?
Emin misin?
Yes! That branch was in the way!
Evet! O dal görüşümü kapatıyordu!
What?!
Ne?!
Usopp...
Usopp-san...
– Captain!
– Kaptan!
Eat this, hypnotist!
Al bakalım, seni hipnozcu!
Get 'im, rubber guy!
Hakla onu, lastik adam!
Kick Captain Kuro's ass!
Kaptan Kuro'nun kıçını tekmele!
Get away!
Bırak!
You guys don't get to cheer for me!
Siz, benim için tezahürat yapmayın!
Let go!
Bırak dedim!
Gum-Gum...
Lastik-Lastik...
Lethal Exploding Star!
Ölümcül Patlayan Yıldız!
My plan...
Planım...
...Bell!
...Çan!
My plan cannot fail!
Planım başarısız olmayacak!!!
As a kid, I had a dream of a dazzling treasure
Çocukken bir hayalim vardı, parlak bir hazine
I had a map in my head that I knew would lead me
Zihnimde saklı bir harita, götürürdü gizlice
Charted a course all on my own, so nobody would beat me
Kimse beni geçmesin diye, çizdim yolu tek başıma
The promised land was in my hand, drew a line in the sand
O vaat edilen diyarda, sınırlar çekildi usulca
Look where I am
Neredeyim bilemem yine…
My one ambition's slipping right through my hands
Hayalim eriyor, sessizce ellerimin içinde
But if the world ever changes I'll call out your name
Ama dünya bir gün değişse bile, çağırırım yine seni
We could return to a time when our lives were still the same
Döneriz belki o günlere, kaybetmediğimiz her anı gibi
Take me to the place where memories remain
Götür beni oraya, anıların solmadığı yere
Please don't ever let them fade
Lütfen unutulmasına asla izin verme